export const questions = [
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answers: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
];